[{"prompt": "Impuses are happy. Sterpus is impus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impuses are happy. Shumpus is numpus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_0": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy.", "layer_1": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_2": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_3": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_4": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_5": "Sam is happy. True", "layer_6": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_7": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_8": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_9": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_10": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_11": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_12": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_13": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_14": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_15": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_16": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_17": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_18": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_19": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_20": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_21": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_22": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_23": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_24": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_25": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_26": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_27": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_28": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_29": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_30": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_31": "Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True"}, {"prompt": "Numpuses are discordant. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are discordant. Impus is rompus. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_0": "Wren is numpus. Wren is discordant. True.", "layer_1": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. True", "layer_2": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_3": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_4": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_5": "Wren is discordant. False", "layer_6": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_7": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_8": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_9": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_10": "Wren is numpuses. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_11": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_12": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_13": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_14": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_15": "Wren is numpuses. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_16": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_17": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_18": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_19": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_20": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_21": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_22": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_23": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_24": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_25": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_26": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_27": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_28": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_29": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_30": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_31": "Wren is numpuses. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Grimpus is lorpus. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_0": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_1": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_2": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_3": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_4": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_5": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_6": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_7": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_8": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_9": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_10": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_11": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_12": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_13": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_14": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_15": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_16": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_17": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_18": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_19": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_20": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_21": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_22": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_23": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_24": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_25": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_26": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_27": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_28": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_29": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_30": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_31": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is loud. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Gorpus is impus. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is loud. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_0": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True.", "layer_1": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_2": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_3": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_4": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_5": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_6": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_7": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_8": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_9": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_10": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_11": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_12": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_13": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_14": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_15": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_16": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_17": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_18": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_19": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_20": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_21": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_22": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_23": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_24": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_25": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_26": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_27": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_28": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_29": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_30": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_31": "Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpuses are spicy. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are spicy. Dumpus is grimpus. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_0": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_1": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_2": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_3": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_4": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_5": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_6": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_7": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_8": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_9": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_10": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_11": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_12": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_13": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_14": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_15": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_16": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_17": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_18": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_19": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_20": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_21": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_22": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_23": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_24": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_25": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_26": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_27": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_28": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_29": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_30": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_31": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True"}, {"prompt": "Jompus is wooden. Impus is jompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Jompus is wooden. Gorpus is shumpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_0": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_1": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_2": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_3": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_4": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_5": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_6": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_7": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_8": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_9": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_10": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_11": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_12": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_13": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_14": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_15": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_16": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_17": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_18": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_19": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_20": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_21": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_22": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_23": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_24": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_25": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_26": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_27": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_28": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_29": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_30": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_31": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are metallic. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are metallic. Tumpus is rompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_0": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True.", "layer_1": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_2": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_3": "Fae is sterpuses. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_4": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_5": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_6": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_7": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_8": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_9": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_10": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_11": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_12": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_13": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_14": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_15": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_16": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_17": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_18": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_19": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_20": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_21": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_22": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_23": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_24": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_25": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_26": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_27": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_28": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_29": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_30": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_31": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True"}, {"prompt": "Impuses are cold. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is cold. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impuses are cold. Sterpus is yumpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is cold. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_0": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_1": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_2": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_3": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_4": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_5": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_6": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_7": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_8": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_9": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_10": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_11": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_12": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_13": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_14": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_15": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_16": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_17": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_18": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_19": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_20": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_21": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_22": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_23": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_24": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_25": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_26": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_27": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_28": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_29": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_30": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_31": "Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True"}, {"prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Vumpus is jompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is impus. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_0": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled.", "layer_1": "Stella is muffled. True", "layer_2": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True.", "layer_3": "Stella is muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_4": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_5": "Stella is muffled. False", "layer_6": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_7": "Stella is muffled. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_8": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_9": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_10": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_11": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_12": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_13": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_14": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_15": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_16": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_17": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_18": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_19": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_20": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_21": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_22": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_23": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_24": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_25": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_26": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_27": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_28": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_29": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_30": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_31": "Stella is dumpuses. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are fruity. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are fruity. Gorpus is lorpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_0": "Alex is grimpus. Alex is fruity. False", "layer_1": "Alex is grimpus. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_2": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_3": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_4": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_5": "Alex is grimpus. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_6": "Alex is grimpus. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_7": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_8": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_9": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_10": "Alex is grimpus. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_11": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_12": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_13": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_14": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_15": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_16": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_17": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_18": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_19": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_20": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_21": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_22": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_23": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_24": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_25": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_26": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_27": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_28": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_29": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_30": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_31": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_1": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_2": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_3": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_4": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_5": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_7": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_8": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_9": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_10": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_11": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_12": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_13": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_14": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_15": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_16": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_17": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_18": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_19": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_20": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_21": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_22": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_23": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_24": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_25": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_26": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_27": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_28": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_29": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_30": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_31": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Vumpus is brimpus. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_0": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy.", "layer_1": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_2": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_3": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_4": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_5": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_6": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_7": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_8": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_9": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_10": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_11": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_12": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_13": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_14": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_15": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_16": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_17": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_18": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_19": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_20": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_21": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_22": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_23": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_24": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_25": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_26": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_27": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_28": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_29": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_30": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_31": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpuses are opaque. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are opaque. Impus is dumpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_0": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True.", "layer_1": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_2": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_3": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_4": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_5": "Stella is opaque. True", "layer_6": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_7": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_8": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_9": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_10": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_11": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_12": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_13": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_14": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_15": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_16": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_17": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_18": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_19": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_20": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_21": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_22": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_23": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_24": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_25": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_26": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_27": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_28": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_29": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_30": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_31": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True"}, {"prompt": "Impuses are slow. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impuses are slow. Jompus is lempus. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_0": "Sam is impus. Sam is slow.", "layer_1": "Sam is impuse. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_2": "Sam is impus. Sam is slow. True", "layer_3": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_4": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_5": "Sam is impuses. Sam is slow. True", "layer_6": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_7": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_8": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_9": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_10": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_11": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_12": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_13": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_14": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_15": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_16": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_17": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_18": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_19": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_20": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_21": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_22": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_23": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_24": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_25": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_26": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_27": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_28": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_29": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_30": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_31": "Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpus is amenable. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is amenable. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is amenable. Dumpus is lempus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is amenable. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_0": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_1": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_2": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_3": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_4": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_5": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_6": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_7": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_8": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_9": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_10": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_11": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_12": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_13": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_14": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_15": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_16": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_17": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_18": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_19": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_20": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_21": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_22": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_23": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_24": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_25": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_26": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_27": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_28": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_29": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_30": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_31": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True"}, {"prompt": "Wumpuses are moderate. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are moderate. Dumpus is lorpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_0": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_1": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_2": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_3": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_4": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_5": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_6": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_7": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_8": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_9": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_10": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_11": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_12": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_13": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_14": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_15": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_16": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_17": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_18": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_19": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_20": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_21": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_22": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_23": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_24": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_25": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_26": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_27": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_28": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_29": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_30": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_31": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True"}, {"prompt": "Zumpus is sweet. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Zumpus is sweet. Impus is jompus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_0": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_1": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_2": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_3": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_4": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_5": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_6": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_7": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_8": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_9": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_10": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_11": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_12": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_13": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_14": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_15": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_16": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_17": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_18": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_19": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_20": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_21": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_22": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_23": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_24": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_25": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_26": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_27": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_28": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_29": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_30": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_31": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True"}, {"prompt": "Impus is fast. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is fast. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impus is fast. Brimpus is lorpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is fast. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_0": "Alex is impus. Alex is fast.", "layer_1": "Alex is impuse. Alex is fast. True", "layer_2": "Alex is impus. Alex is fast. True", "layer_3": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_4": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_5": "Alex is fast. True", "layer_6": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_7": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_8": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_9": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_10": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_11": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_12": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_13": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_14": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_15": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_16": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_17": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_18": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_19": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_20": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_21": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_22": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_23": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_24": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_25": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_26": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_27": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_28": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_29": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_30": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_31": "Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are transparent. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are transparent. Wumpus is rompus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True.", "layer_1": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_3": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_12": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_13": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_14": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_15": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_16": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_17": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_18": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_19": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_20": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_21": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_22": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_23": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_24": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_25": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_26": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_27": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_28": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_29": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_30": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_31": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True"}, {"prompt": "Vumpuses are dull. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is blue. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are dull. Brimpus is grimpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is blue. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_0": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_1": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_2": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_3": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_4": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_5": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_6": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_7": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_8": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_9": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_10": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_11": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_12": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_13": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_14": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_15": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_16": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_17": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_18": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_19": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_20": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_21": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_22": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_23": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_24": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_25": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_26": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_27": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_28": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_29": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_30": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_31": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is yumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Brimpus is lorpus. Alex is yumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_0": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_1": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_2": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_3": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_4": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_5": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_6": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_7": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_8": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_9": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_10": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_11": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_12": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_13": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_14": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_15": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_16": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_17": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_18": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_19": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_20": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_21": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_22": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_23": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_24": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_25": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_26": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_27": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_28": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_29": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_30": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_31": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are small. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are small. Tumpus is gorpus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_0": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_1": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_2": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_3": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_4": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_5": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_6": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_7": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_8": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_9": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_10": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_11": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_12": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_13": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_14": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_15": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_16": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_17": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_18": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_19": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_20": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_21": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_22": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_23": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_24": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_25": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_26": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_27": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_28": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_29": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_30": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_31": "Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True"}, {"prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Lempus is sterpus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_0": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is happy. True.", "layer_1": "Alex is gorpuses. Alex is happy. True", "layer_2": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is dull. False", "layer_3": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_4": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is dull. False", "layer_5": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is happy. True", "layer_6": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is dull. False", "layer_7": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_8": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_9": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_10": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is happy. True", "layer_11": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is dull. False", "layer_12": "Alex is gorpuses. Alex is happy. True", "layer_13": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_14": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_15": "Alex is gorpuses. Alex is happy. True", "layer_16": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is dull. False", "layer_17": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_18": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_19": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_20": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_21": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_22": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_23": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_24": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_25": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_26": "Alex is gorpus. Alex is dull. False", "layer_27": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_28": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_29": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_30": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_31": "Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False"}, {"prompt": "Numpus is earthy. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Numpus is earthy. Brimpus is zumpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_0": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are earthy. Alex is earthy. True.", "layer_1": "Alex is numpuses. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_2": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_3": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_4": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_5": "Alex is numpus. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_6": "Alex is numpus. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_7": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_8": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_9": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_10": "Alex is numpus. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_11": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_12": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_13": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_14": "Alex is numpuses. Numpuses are earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_15": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_16": "Alex is numpuses. Numpuses are earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_17": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_18": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_19": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_20": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_21": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_22": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_23": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_24": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_25": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_26": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_27": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_28": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_29": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_30": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_31": "Alex is numpuses. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Gorpus is wumpus. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_0": "Wren is grimpus. Impus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True.", "layer_1": "Wren is grimpus. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_2": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_3": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_4": "Wren is grimpus. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_5": "Wren is grimpus. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_6": "Wren is grimpus. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_7": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_8": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_9": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_10": "Wren is grimpus. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_11": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_12": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_13": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_14": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_15": "Wren is grimpus. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_16": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_17": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_18": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_19": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_20": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_21": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_22": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_23": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_24": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_25": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_26": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_27": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_28": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_29": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_30": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_31": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True"}, {"prompt": "Vumpuses are fruity. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are fruity. Tumpus is gorpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_0": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity.", "layer_1": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_2": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_3": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_4": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_5": "Max is fruity. True", "layer_6": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_7": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_8": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_9": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_10": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_11": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_12": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_13": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_14": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_15": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_16": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_17": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_18": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_19": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_20": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_21": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_22": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_23": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_24": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_25": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_26": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_27": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_28": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_29": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_30": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_31": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True"}, {"prompt": "Rompuses are brown. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is lorpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are brown. Yumpus is wumpus. Sam is lorpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_0": "Rompus is brown. Sam is brown.", "layer_1": "Sam is rompus. Sam is brown. True", "layer_2": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True.", "layer_3": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_4": "Sam is rompus. Rompus are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_5": "Sam is brown. False", "layer_6": "Rompus is brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_7": "Sam is rompus. Rompus are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_8": "Rompus is brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_9": "Sam is rompus. Rompus are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_10": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_11": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_12": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_13": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_14": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_15": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_16": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_17": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_18": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_19": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_20": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_21": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_22": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_23": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_24": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_25": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_26": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_27": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_28": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_29": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_30": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_31": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Yumpus is zumpus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_0": "Sam is grimpus. Impuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_1": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_2": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_3": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_4": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_5": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_7": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_8": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_9": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_10": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_11": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_12": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_13": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_14": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_15": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_16": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_17": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_18": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_19": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_20": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_21": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_22": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_23": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_24": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_25": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_26": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_27": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_28": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_29": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_30": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_31": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True"}, {"prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Zumpus is gorpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_0": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_1": "Alex is jompus. Alex is dull. True", "layer_2": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_3": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_4": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_5": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_6": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_7": "Alex is jompus. Alex is dull. True", "layer_8": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_9": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_10": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_11": "Alex is jompus. Alex is dull. True", "layer_12": "Alex is jompus. Alex is dull. True", "layer_13": "Alex is jompus. Alex is dull. True", "layer_14": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_15": "Alex is jompus. Alex is dull. True", "layer_16": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_17": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_18": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_19": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_20": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_21": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_22": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_23": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_24": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_25": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_26": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_27": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_28": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_29": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_30": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_31": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpus is muffled. Impus is yumpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is muffled. Zumpus is sterpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is impus. Impus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_0": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_1": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_2": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_3": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_4": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_5": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_6": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_7": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_8": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_9": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_10": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_11": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_12": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_13": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_14": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_15": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_16": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_17": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_18": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_19": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_20": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_21": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_22": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_23": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_24": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_25": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_26": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_27": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_28": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_29": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_30": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_31": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are small. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are small. Yumpus is vumpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_0": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small.", "layer_1": "Stella is sterpus. Stella is small. True", "layer_2": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True.", "layer_3": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_4": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_5": "Stella is small. False", "layer_6": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_7": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_8": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_9": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_10": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_11": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_12": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_13": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_14": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_15": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_16": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_17": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_18": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_19": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_20": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_21": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_22": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_23": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_24": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_25": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_26": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_27": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_28": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_29": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_30": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_31": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True"}, {"prompt": "Rompus is large. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Rompus is large. Yumpus is sterpus. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is impus. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_0": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_1": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_2": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_3": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_4": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_5": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_6": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_7": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are large. Alex is large. True", "layer_8": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_9": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_10": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_11": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_12": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_13": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_14": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_15": "Alex is rompuses. Rompuses are large. Alex is large. True", "layer_16": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_17": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_18": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_19": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_20": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_21": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_22": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_23": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_24": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_25": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_26": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_27": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_28": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_29": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_30": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_31": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True"}, {"prompt": "Rompuses are transparent. Impus is rompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are transparent. Wumpus is brimpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is rompus. Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Rompus is transparent. Stella is transparent.", "layer_1": "Stella is rompus. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True.", "layer_3": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Stella is transparent. False", "layer_6": "Rompus is transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Stella is rompus. Rompus are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_12": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_13": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_14": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_15": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_16": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_17": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_18": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_19": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_20": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_21": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_22": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_23": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_24": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_25": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_26": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_27": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_28": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_29": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_30": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_31": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True"}, {"prompt": "Impus is transparent. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impus is transparent. Dumpus is yumpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Rex is impus. Rex is transparent.", "layer_1": "Impuses are transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Rex is impus. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_3": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Rex is impusus. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_6": "Rex is impus. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Rex is impus. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_12": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_13": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_14": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_15": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_16": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_17": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_18": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_19": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_20": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_21": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_22": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_23": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_24": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_25": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_26": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_27": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_28": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_29": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_30": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_31": "Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Tumpus is lempus. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_0": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_1": "Wren is sterpuses. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_2": "Wren is sterpuses. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_3": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_4": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_5": "Wren is sterpuses. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_6": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_7": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_8": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_9": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_10": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_11": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_12": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_13": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_14": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_15": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_16": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_17": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_18": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_19": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_20": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_21": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_22": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_23": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_24": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_25": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_26": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_27": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_28": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_29": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_30": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_31": "Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True"}, {"prompt": "Shumpuses are floral. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is floral. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are floral. Jompus is zumpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is floral. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_0": "Rex is shumpus. Rex is floral. Rex is floral. True or false: Rex is floral.", "layer_1": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_2": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_3": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_4": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_5": "Rex is shump. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_6": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_7": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_8": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_9": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_10": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_11": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_12": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_13": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_14": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_15": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_16": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_17": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_18": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_19": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_20": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_21": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_22": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_23": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_24": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_25": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_26": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_27": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_28": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_29": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_30": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_31": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True"}, {"prompt": "Wumpuses are cold. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is cold. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are cold. Gorpus is sterpus. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is cold. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_0": "Wren is wumpus. Wren is cold. True.", "layer_1": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_2": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_3": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_4": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_5": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_6": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_7": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_8": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_9": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_10": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_11": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_12": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_13": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_14": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_15": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_16": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_17": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_18": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_19": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_20": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_21": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_22": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_23": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_24": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_25": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_26": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_27": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_28": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_29": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_30": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_31": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True"}, {"prompt": "Wumpuses are slow. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is lorpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are slow. Tumpus is sterpus. Alex is lorpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_0": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_1": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_2": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_3": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_4": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_5": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_6": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_7": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_8": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_9": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_10": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_11": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_12": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_13": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_14": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_15": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_16": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_17": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_18": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_19": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_20": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_21": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_22": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_23": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_24": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_25": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_26": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_27": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_28": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_29": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_30": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_31": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Lempus is numpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Vumpus is shumpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_0": "Alex is numpus. Alex is sweet.", "layer_1": "Alex is numpus. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_2": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_3": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_4": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_5": "Alex is numpus. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_6": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_7": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_8": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_9": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_10": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_11": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_12": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_13": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_14": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_15": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_16": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_17": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_18": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_19": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_20": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_21": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_22": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_23": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_24": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_25": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_26": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_27": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_28": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_29": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_30": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_31": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is snowy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Zumpus is tumpus. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is snowy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. False", "layer_0": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_1": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_2": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_3": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_4": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_5": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_6": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_7": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_8": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_9": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_10": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_11": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_12": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_13": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_14": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_15": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_16": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_17": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_18": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_19": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_20": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_21": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_22": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_23": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_24": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_25": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_26": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_27": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_28": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_29": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_30": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_31": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpuses are bitter. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are bitter. Shumpus is sterpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. False", "layer_0": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True.", "layer_1": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_2": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_3": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_4": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_5": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_6": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_7": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_8": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. False", "layer_9": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_10": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_11": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_12": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. False", "layer_13": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_14": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_15": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_16": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_17": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_18": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_19": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_20": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_21": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_22": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_23": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_24": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_25": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_26": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_27": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_28": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_29": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_30": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_31": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True"}, {"prompt": "Lempuses are bitter. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are bitter. Zumpus is numpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_0": "Sam is lempus. Empuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True.", "layer_1": "Sam is lempus. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_2": "Sam is lempus. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_3": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_4": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_5": "Sam is lempus. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_6": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_7": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_8": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_9": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_10": "Sam is lempus. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_11": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_12": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_13": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_14": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_15": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_16": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_17": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_18": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_19": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_20": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_21": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_22": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_23": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_24": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_25": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_26": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_27": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_28": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_29": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_30": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_31": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True"}, {"prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is slow. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Brimpus is gorpus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is slow. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_0": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_1": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_2": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_3": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_4": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_5": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_6": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_7": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_8": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_9": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_10": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_11": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_12": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_13": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_14": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_15": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_16": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_17": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_18": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_19": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_20": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_21": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_22": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_23": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_24": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_25": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_26": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_27": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_28": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_29": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_30": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_31": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpus is cold. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is cold. Lorpus is dumpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_0": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are cold. Alex is cold. True.", "layer_1": "Alex is tumpus. True", "layer_2": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_3": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_4": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_5": "Alex is cold. True", "layer_6": "Alex is tumpus. Alex is cold. True", "layer_7": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_8": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_9": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_10": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_11": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_12": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_13": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_14": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_15": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_16": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_17": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_18": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_19": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_20": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_21": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_22": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_23": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_24": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_25": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_26": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_27": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_28": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_29": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_30": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_31": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True"}, {"prompt": "Gorpuses are luminous. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are luminous. Tumpus is zumpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_0": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_1": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_2": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_3": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_4": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_5": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_6": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_7": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_8": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_9": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_10": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_11": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_12": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_13": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_14": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_15": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_16": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_17": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_18": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_19": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_20": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_21": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_22": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_23": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_24": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_25": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_26": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_27": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_28": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_29": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_30": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_31": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True"}, {"prompt": "Lempus is hot. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is hot. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Lempus is hot. Numpus is gorpus. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is hot. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_0": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_1": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_2": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_3": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_4": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_5": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_6": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_7": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_8": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_9": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_10": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_11": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_12": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_13": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_14": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_15": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_16": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_17": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_18": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_19": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_20": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_21": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_22": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_23": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_24": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_25": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_26": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_27": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_28": "Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_29": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_30": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True", "layer_31": "Sam is lempus. Sam is hot. True"}, {"prompt": "Lempuses are transparent. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are transparent. Rompus is brimpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Sam is lempus. Empuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True.", "layer_1": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_3": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_6": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True"}]